https://www.aquajogger.com/home/aquajogger-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
– If you are having trouble ordering on our website, check out our Online Ordering Help section
– If you have a question, check out our FAQ (Frequently Asked Question) section.
– If you cannot find the help you need online, feel free to contact us.
AQUAJOGGER’S COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY: WE SHARE NOTHING
This site is owned and operated by AquaJogger.
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At AquaJogger, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
INFORMATION AQUAJOGGER GATHERS AND TRACKS
AquaJogger gathers two types of information about users:
Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in product sweepstakes, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys.
Information AquaJogger gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does AquaJogger divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.
AquaJogger Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:
OPTIONAL VOLUNTARY INFORMATION
We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:
1. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)
We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. AquaJogger gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. As a courtesy to our customer, we subscribe those who order online. Users may remove themselves anytime from this mailing list by following the instructions provided in every newsletter.
2. “E-mail this to a friend” Service
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking “e-mail this to a friend”. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.
CHILDREN
Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.
USAGE TRACKING
AquaJogger tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. AquaJogger does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).
AquaJogger sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
COOKIES
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. AquaJogger uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our ordering process also uses cookies to determine which items have been placed in the shoping cart, and this information is never used for anything else.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to shop online at this site.
AQUAJOGGER’S USE OF INFORMATION
AquaJogger uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.
As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters. AquaJogger never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.
When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.
SECURITY
AquaJogger operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.
OPT-OUT POLICY
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:
Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users
YOUR CONSENT
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by AquaJogger. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Scroll To Top
